I say, welcome brothers and sisters to
another Wednesday question and answer
where we open up with the 10
Commandments that God commanded for the
whole world to keep. Brother James. Yes,
sir.
And God speak all these words saying, I
am the Lord thy God, which have brought
thee out of the land of Egypt, out of
the house of bondage. Thou shall have no
other gods before me. Thou shall not
make unto thee any graven image or any
likeness of anything that is in heaven
above or that is in the earth beneath or
that is in the water under the earth.
Thou shall not bow down thyself to them
nor serve them. For I the Lord thy God
am a jealous God, visiting the iniquity
of the fathers upon the children unto
the third and fourth generation of them
that hate me and showing mercy unto
thousands of them that love me and keep
my commandments. Thou shall not take the
name of the Lord thy God in vain. For
the Lord will not hold him guiltless
that taketh his name in vain.
Remember the Sabbath day to keep it
holy. Six days shall thou labor and do
all thy work. But the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In it thou
shall not do any work, thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter, thy man servant nor
thy maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates.
For in six days the Lord made heaven and
earth, the sea and all that in them is
and rested the seventh day. Wherefore
the Lord blessed the Sabbath day and
hollowed it. Honor thy father and thy
mother that thy days may be long upon
the land which the Lord thy God giveth
thee. Thou shall not kill. Thou shall
not commit adultery. Thou shall not
steal. Thou shall not bear false witness
against thy neighbor. Thou shall not
covet thy neighbor's house nor thou
shall not covet thy neighbor's wife nor
his man servant nor his maid servant nor
his ox nor his ass nor anything that is
thy neighbor's.
I read Exodus 20 verses 1 through 17.
May the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of this word. In Jesus' name we
pray. Amen.
Amen. Amen.
So here on question and answer, you can
ask us a question and we'll answer it
according to the King James Bible. And
if we cannot find the answer, we will
seek further counsel to bring you an
answer at a later time.
The questions we will not answer are the
vague and the long scripture questions
as well as questions of debate. We are
not here to debate. We are here to
spread the true gospel of Jesus. So
please be as direct as possible with
your questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible. No other Bibles or
books will be acknowledged on this
program. Also keep in mind this is a
live stream so feel free to send in your
questions that pertain to everlasting
life. We just ask that you please keep
them to a two scripture maximum. So let
me introduce to you the family that's on
the panel this evening. Brother Jerome.
Grace and peace.
Brother Dre.
Good evening.
Brother Julius. Good evening, everybody.
Brother James.
Good evening, everyone.
Sister Deborah.
Good evening.
Brother Shawn.
And we have the guest caller with us and
I'm brother Cornell. Sister Deborah,
what is our first question of the
evening?
Uh yes, there are several held over
questions that will be answered first
before getting into tonight's Q&A.
Angela Clayton says, "Someone asked a
question during the May 14, 2025 Q&A,
if baptism is required.
The response did not include scripture.
Please provide scripture that indicates
that baptism is required."
All right. So
they say that it was not put in there on
May the 14th, but we will put it in
there this evening. Brother Jerome, what
you got?
Yes, let's um let's do that. Let's go to
Matthew is the third chapter.
And this is John the Baptist
speaking to
Jesus Christ
at the time where he was baptizing
Jesus.
Matthew is the third chapter. Pick it up
at verse 13, read it to the 15.
Then cometh
Then cometh Jesus from Galilee to Jordan
unto John to be baptized of him.
But John forbade him saying, "I have
need to be baptized of thee and cometh
thou to me?"
And Jesus answering said unto him,
"Suffer it to be so now for thus it
becometh us to fulfill all
righteousness." Then he suffered him.
Okay. So
you understand that Jesus is letting us
all know suffer it to be so
to fulfill all righteousness and part of
us establishing righteousness
is to get baptized in the name of Jesus,
okay? Now Jesus
is the prophet that Moses told you about
and he said whoever don't listen to that
prophet
he said they're going to be destroyed
and Jesus is the prophet. Okay, so let's
go to Acts the third chapter.
And we're going to read verse 22 and
we're going to skip.
Okay.
Go ahead.
For Moses truly said unto the fathers,
"A prophet shall the Lord your God raise
up unto you of your brethren like unto
me. Him shall ye hear in all things
whatsoever he shall say unto you." Mhm,
he told us suffer it to be so, get
baptized, right?
Skip down to verse 26.
Unto your Unto you first God having
raised up his son Jesus sent him to
bless you in turning away every one of
you from his iniquities. Mhm, now skip
up and read verse 23 and that'll be it.
And it shall come to pass that every
soul which will not hear that prophet
shall be destroyed from among the
people.
And that's all I got.
All right.
throw in one other thing.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Go to Mark 16 and read verse 16.
Okay, Mark 16 and verse 16 says,
"He that believeth and is baptized shall
be saved. But he that believeth not
shall be damned."
That's enough.
Yep.
All right.
And that lets us know that hey, his
sheep hear his voice and follow him.
All right.
Thank you for that. We hope that
answered your question as we continue to
move on.
Moving on. John Noel says, "I've been
reading my Bible starting at Genesis.
Now I'm reading Mark chapter 7 verses 14
through 23. Jesus says nothing you put
in your mouth will defile you. So what
does this mean to the dietary law?"
All right, brother Julius. We know that
dietary law is still intact. What you
got, brother? Share some light. Uh uh
good evening, everybody. Exactly,
brother Cornell. Uh
uh the the person asking the question
says, "Nothing you put in your mouth
will defile you, then why did God give
you a dietary law?"
Because you uh
but this right here, this scripture
Let's go to Mark the seventh chapter
because this has nothing to do with the
dietary law. And this is where a lot of
people get confused.
But let's look at what Jesus said,
James. Mark 7, we're going to pick it up
at
uh verse 14. Verse 14 uh cuz we're going
to uh read her script uh this person's
scripture and then the answer is right
there in the same chapter. Go ahead at
13. Look what Jesus said. Go ahead.
Making the word of God of none effect
through your
start start at 14.
Okay. And when he had called all the
people unto him, he said unto them,
"Harken unto me every one of you and
understand." And do what? Understand.
Understand what you're about to read. Go
ahead.
There is nothing from without a man that
entering into him can defile him. Now
underline the word underline the word
defile him.
Nothing
defile him. We're talking about defile.
Go ahead.
But the things which come out of him,
those are they that defile the man. And
Jesus finna tell you something else at
16 again.
If any man have ears to hear, let him
hear. See, this is a parable. How do we
know? Read the next verse and continue
to read. And when he was entered into
the house from the people, his disciples
asked him concerning the parable.
Because they understood they didn't they
didn't understand at first.
They thought the same thing that this
person uh uh probably thinking about
this that and do with food that you eat.
No, keep reading.
And he saith unto them, are ye so
without understanding also?
Do ye not perceive that whatsoever thing
from without entereth into the man, it
cannot defile him? This ain't got
nothing to do with food. What does this
really have to do with? Read skip down
to verse 20 and continue
to 23. Go ahead. And he said, that which
cometh out of the man, that defileth the
man. Now, now what comes out of the of a
man that can defile him? Go ahead.
For from within, out of the heart of
man, proceed evil thoughts, Oh, evil
thoughts.
The heart, the mind. What come out your
mind?
Evil thoughts. Go ahead.
adulteries, adulteries,
fornications, Yes. murders, You got to
think about these things first. Go
ahead.
thefts, covetousness, wickedness,
deceit, lasciviousness, an I an evil
eye, Yes. blasphemy, pride, foolishness.
Yes. All all these evil things come from
within and defile the man. It is within
your mind, but then when it comes out of
your mind, it gets into your mind, then
you act on those. Now you are defiled.
Now you are defiled. And he said verse
23, all these evil things come from
within. They in you. They in your mind.
And when you act on now you are defiled.
In another scripture, he told you if you
look upon a woman to lust after after
her, you have committed adultery in your
heart. Because the mind system,
brothers, have nothing to do with the
food. It's the evil thoughts. That's
what come in your mind and that's what
defile you. That's all I got, Cornell.
Yes, sir.
All right, brother. Thank you for that
good light. Hope that answered their
question as we continue to move on to
our next.
Next one, Alyssa Ellington says or asks,
is it idolatry
or a provision
to that sin if pastors make posters and
have them hung up
at the entrance of the church?
All right, brother Dre. What about these
posters hung up at the entrance of the
church? What you say, brother? Is that
idolatry?
No, it is not idolatry.
You know, uh
can it provide a pathway to idolatry?
If if someone is looking, you know, at
the pastor
worshipping him, that's that's a whole
'nother thing, but what it is is is is
vanity.
Because it is not about the pastor,
it should be about the word of God.
That's right.
Matthew 23. Matthew 23 and we going to
pick it up at verse one.
It's problematic
when it becomes about the pastor.
The pastor ministers the word of God.
That's what it's about. It's not about a
pastor, but to have a picture up
don't have nothing to do with idolatry
unless you worshipping it.
So,
start at verse one, brother. Go ahead.
Then spake Jesus to the multitude and to
his disciples,
saying, the scribes and Pharisees sit in
Moses' seat.
Yes, go ahead. All therefore whatsoever
they bid you observe, that observe and
do, but do not ye after their works, for
they say and do not. So, whatever they
bid you to do it within the word of God,
you do it, but don't do after their
works because they say and do not. Skip
down to verse five. Go ahead.
But all their works they do for to be
seen of men.
They make broad their phylacteries and
enlarge the borders of their garments.
Go ahead. And love the uppermost rooms
at feast and the chief seats in the
synagogues. Go ahead. And greetings in
the markets and to be called of men
rabbi, rabbi.
So, this is what this is about, vain
glory.
Because that is vanity. The book tells
you
they do their works to be seen of men.
They make broad their phylacteries.
Their fringes are their garments.
And they look to be looked at in in and
have the chief seats in the synagogue
and to be rabbi, which is master.
Read the next verse, brother. Go ahead.
But be not ye called rabbi, for one is
your master, even Christ, and all ye are
brethren. That's right. So, no man
should be called rabbi.
What's wrong with brother? When you come
to the Israel of God, you notice
brothers are called brother.
Not rabbi, not reverend.
The book tells you in Psalms 111 and 9
that reverend and holy is God's name.
And these are flattering titles
that leave men puffed up
and vain.
But and and some fall into worship. They
have churches named after them. Read
just a little bit more. Go ahead,
brother.
And call no man your father upon the
earth, for one is your father which is
in heaven.
So, one is your father.
So, you church that call not only their
priest father, but they call their head
priest holy father.
Mhm.
Not so. Not so. Read a little more,
brother. Go ahead.
Neither be ye called master, for one is
your master, even Christ.
Go ahead. But he that is greatest among
you shall be your servant.
He that is greatest among you shall be
your servant. So, the pictures
are not
idolatry,
but can they provide a provision to the
pathway of that? A lot of this stuff
can. Calling a man these, giving them
these titles. I got one other place.
Job 32 verses 21 and 22.
Read that when you get it, brother. Job
32 21 and 22.
Okay, it says, let me not, I pray you,
accept any man's person, neither let me
give flattering titles unto man.
For I know not to give flattering
titles, in so doing my maker would soon
take me away.
So, the flattering titles, the pictures,
all this vain stuff to be puffed up is
not We should be glorifying the God of
Israel, not us. That's all I got.
Mhm.
All right, brother.
That's some good light there. Hope that
answers your question as we move on to
our next.
Moving on. Uh Kim Noel asks, is there a
difference between someone who is not
following the word of God, but resist
taking the mark of the beast and the
thief on the cross and repenting on
their deathbed?
All right, quite a bit into that
question there.
I'm going to ask caller to share some
light.
Okay, the first thing is
why
would
they resist taking the mark
of the beast unless they have some
knowledge?
That's right.
It's all that simple. Now, otherwise,
if they say you got to get a mark to buy
or sell
and you
don't have no understanding,
you say, "So what? Put the mark on me
so you can buy or sell." So, now that
imply to me
these people will not serve God, but
still they going to resist the mark of
the beast. That imply to me they
willfully
and intentionally wouldn't serve God.
If that's the case,
let me give you something. Let's go into
Matthew and and you think that they
going to get salvation like the last day
of the thief? I'm going to tell you
something. That thief had some
knowledge.
Yep.
I know because what he made a question
Jesus.
He said
and he first thing is he told his
partner, "Hey, we belong up here."
And the one thing you don't know why he
was stealing. He was a he was a stealing
under the
uh
slavery under the Roman Empire.
But the thing that let me know he had
some some some understanding, he didn't
ask Jesus to take him to heaven.
He said
"When you come into thy kingdom,
remember me." That let me know that guy
knew that Jesus is going to have a
kingdom on this earth for 1,000 years.
Yep. He asked a question, his heart was
in the right place, but he had some
knowledge.
So, now
as far as this thief is concerned is
this person that ain't serving God,
he have some kind of knowledge. And this
one thing he should know. Let's go into
Matthew the 19th chapter and read verses
16 and 17.
Okay, Matthew 19 and verse 16 and 17
says,
"And behold, one came and said unto him,
Good master, what good thing shall I do
that I may have eternal life?"
And he said unto him, "Why callest thou
me good? There is none good but one,
that is God. But if thou will enter into
life, keep the commandments."
So it's okay then. You want to know how
to get eternal life? Keep the
commandments.
So it's obvious if this person don't
have been
dealing with the word of God, he is not
keeping the commandments.
But if he have knowledge
and is not keeping it, let's see what's
going to happen. Go to Hebrews the 10th
chapter.
Read verses
26 and 27.
Hebrews the 10th chapter,
verses 26 and 27 says, "For if we sin
willfully after that we have received
the knowledge of the truth, there
remaineth no more sacrifice for sins,
but a certain fearful looking for of
judgment and fiery indignation, which
shall devour devour the adversaries."
Okay now.
This this this this Let's think about
what you just read here.
If you have some knowledge
and you still are not walking in the
word of God, it says right here, you
sinning willfully.
And the place that you have coming is in
lake of fire.
Mhm. So the Lord is going to do one
thing, and it's for the living and the
dead. Let's go to Revelation the 20th
chapter and read verse 11 and 12.
Revelation 20, verses 11 and 12 says,
"And I saw a great white throne, and him
that sat on it, from whose face the
earth and the heaven fled away, and
there was found no place for them."
"And I saw the dead, small and great,
stand before God, and the books were
opened, and another book was opened,
which is the book of life. And the dead
were judged out of those things which
were written in the books according to
their works."
So now,
you're going to be judged
by the thing that's written in this
book, and this in the book, that's the
Bible.
According to your works. So you're
talking about repenting on the last day
of your life?
It depends on your knowledge. It depends
on what you've been doing.
We don't know what the thief thief did
that the Lord would say give him eternal
life at the last day, but we know one
thing,
if a guy with
went all his life
not serving God
and he got a little knowledge
to receive to reject the knowledge to
the
uh
mark of the beast,
he's in trouble.
Whether the Lord save him or not,
we're going to leave that to the Lord.
Don't have to say.
All right.
We hope that that answered your question
there. As we move on to our next
question.
Next question, Sam Burns asks for some
clarity concerning Isaiah 25 verse 7.
All right, brother Julius. Isaiah 25
verse 7.
Let's read that uh James. Okay.
Isaiah 25 and verse 7 says, "And he will
destroy in this mountain the face of the
covering cast over all people, and the
veil that is spread over all nations."
That is talking about
all the lies, all the doctrines, all the
religions, everything that Satan
established. And this is And this is
dated. It dates itself. Continue to read
to the verse 9. Go ahead and read.
"He will swallow up death in victory,
and the Lord God will wipe away tears
from off all faces. And the rebuke of
his people shall he take away from off
all the earth, for the Lord has spoken
it." This is talking about at the return
of the Lord, when he take over the
kingdom of this world, he's going to
destroy all of Satan's work, the
deceptions, the lies, the myths, the
fables, all the doctrines, false
doctrines. And one more verse at verse
9. Go ahead.
"And it shall be said in that day, Lo,
this is our God. We have waited for him,
and he will save us. This is the Lord,
we have waited for him, we will be glad
and rejoice in his salvation."
And that is at the return of the Lord,
but it told you up there at verse 7, and
he will destroy in the mountain the face
of the covering cast over all people.
What covering? Whose covering? Isaiah 30
and just one verse and I'm done.
Let's see what the And the And it still
exists today. That covering is still
exists today because
uh the majority of the religions and the
things that we have in this world, this
Satan is the god of this world, that's a
little g.
Isaiah 30 and 1. Go ahead.
"Woe to the rebellious children, saith
the Lord, that take counsel, but not of
me, and that cover with a covering, but
not of my spirit, that they may add sin
to sin." So this is Satan's covering.
All this stuff, this is Satan's world.
This is Satan's doctrine. So they are
covered with Satan's spirit, and when
the Lord come, he's going to take all of
that stuff and we're going to be in the
kingdom where in dwells righteousness
and knowledge and understanding and true
worship of the God of Israel. That's all
I got, Cornell.
All right. It'll be some rejoicing and
singing during that time, brother.
That's right.
Yes, sir. All right, we hope that
answered your question there. As we move
on to our next one.
Next one, Jennifer Love asks, "In
Genesis 5, when it talks about how long
the generations of Adam lived,
are these the years as we count them
now?"
Yeah, yeah, they The day is a day and
it takes weeks to make months and months
to make years, and yeah, we we still on
that. So let's go on
Luke the 2nd chapter. Luke 2.
And let's follow
the master as he was coming up. Let's
see what it says about him.
Luke 2.
And when you get there, brother, pick it
up at that verse
uh 40 for me.
Because this is the one
who got off his holy throne and came and
put on his filthy flesh to die for man.
Luke 2
and 40. Go ahead.
"And the child grew, and waxed strong in
spirit, filled with wisdom. And the
grace of God was upon him."
Go ahead.
"Now his parents went to Jerusalem every
year at the feast of the Passover." So
this is Jesus and this is his parents,
Joseph and Mary. Go ahead.
"And when he was 12 years old, they went
up to Jerusalem after the custom of the
feast." So he had a number here, 12
years old, and it took 12 months for a
year, and hey, he was 12 years old here.
Read the next verse.
"And when they had fulfilled the days as
they returned, the child Jesus tarried
behind in Jerusalem, and Joseph and his
mother knew not of it."
All right, so let's go to Luke 3.
Luke 3, and let's pick it up at that
verse
21.
Luke 3 and 21.
Go ahead.
"Now when all the people were baptized,
it came to pass that Jesus also, being
baptized and praying, the heaven was
opened." Jesus' baptism. Go ahead.
"And the Holy Ghost descended in a
bodily shape like a dove upon him, and a
voice came from heaven, which said, Thou
art my beloved son, in thee I am well
pleased." Yeah, it goes back to what
Jerome was saying about baptism being
necessary. The master did it, hey, it's
good for us. How old was he? Because he
was 12 at first, now we're talking 18
years
later. Go ahead.
"And Jesus himself began to be about 30
years of age, being, as was supposed,
the son of Joseph, which was the son of
Heli."
So it's the it's the days and then the
weeks and the months and the years that
determines
our age, and so it is the same.
I haven't seen any change in it, and
that's all I got. Anybody else?
All right, we're going to leave it right
there. Hope that answered your question.
As we move on with a time check to our
next one.
Yes, moving on, the time is 8:02. She
also wants you to explain Genesis 32
verses 30 through 32.
All right, let's help Jennifer out here,
brother Jerome, in that Genesis
32:30-32.
Let's go read it.
I'm there.
Go ahead and read.
"And Jacob called the name of the place
Peniel, for I have seen God face to
face, and my life is preserved.
And as he passed over Peniel, the sun
rose upon him, and he halted upon his
thigh.
Therefore, the children of Israel eat
not of the sinew which shrank, which is
support which is upon the hollow of the
thigh unto this day, because he touched
the hollow of Jacob's thigh and the
sinew that shrank.
And that verse
30, it mentions about the face to face.
Well,
the Lord sent an angel,
um,
before Jacob.
And that angel asked him what was his
name. To make a long story short, he was
adopted at that point
at that time. His name was changed from
Jacob to Israel. But it said face to
face right there. Okay? It don't mean
that he literally seeing the face of
God. Okay? The Lord got an angel that's
uh and he's called the angel of the
Lord's presence. Okay?
So, that verse said face to face, that
don't mean you literally seeing seeing
the face of God. And there's another
place in Deuteronomy. Let's go to that
Deuteronomy. Talked about the whole
nation of Israel when they was on um
Mount Horeb, which is Mount Sinai. Uh
Deuteronomy chapter five.
And let's and let's read verse one
through five. Okay.
When you get it, go ahead and read.
Deuteronomy 5:1-5 says, "And Moses
called all Israel and said unto them,
Hear, O Israel, the statutes and
judgments which I speak in your ears
this day, that ye may learn them, and
keep and do them.
The Lord our God made a covenant with us
in Horeb.
The Lord made not his covenant with our
fathers, but with us, even us, who are
all of us here alive this day.
The Lord talked with you face to face in
the mount out of the midst of the fire.
Yeah, so even right there, all all of
Israel,
they was the Lord was present right
there with them, literally. But they
didn't literally see him. He was
actually behind a pillar cloud and uh
and fire. But he was right there and it
represented face to face. Okay? Right
there. All right? Now, in regards to
that verse 31 and 32 in your
question,
it you know, it's a custom it was a
custom then among Israel, but it wasn't
a law neither was it a
is a it a commandment given by God for
for all to keep. Okay?
And that's all I got.
All right.
Thank you for that, brother. Hope that
answered that question as we move on to
the next one.
Next one, Keshia Lee says, "I watched
the Bible lesson Saturday, death and
resurrection,
and I'm still confused on why man was
created. Can you please explain?"
All right. Can you cast some light,
guest caller, on that question?
The first thing is
if uh
if you confused,
you do this because you don't uh
believe what you hear.
Still,
man was created to be God.
I have a lesson out there titled that.
And it's based on this
on these scriptures. Let's go to
Psalms chapter 82.
We're going to read one and two.
Then we're going to skip down and read
six and seven.
Okay.
Psalm 82:1-2
says, "God standeth in the congregation
of the mighty. He judge- judgeth among
the gods."
All right there. Right there. I want to
make make make have a look at that. Who
were these congregation of the mighty
and who were these gods? It's plural
that he was talking about.
Maybe the two in the godhead, the Father
and the Son. But whoever these p-
these uh individuals are, he called them
the congregation of the mighty and he
judges among the gods. Go ahead.
How long will ye judge unjustly and
accept the persons of the wicked?
And he asking that question. Then look
what he says. Skip down and read six and
seven.
I have said, "Ye are gods and are on all
are of you are children of the Most
High.
But ye shall die like men and fall like
one of the princes."
And this is God talking to these
individuals. He said, "I have said you
are gods and all of you are children of
the Most High.
But you going to die like men."
So, the only thing only a being that's
here and is dying right now is us. The
angels are not dying.
So, he wasn't talking to the angels.
Let's go into Saint John the 10th
chapter
and uh let Jesus put put a little
clarification on it. Saint John 10
and we going to read verses 23 to 25.
Then we're going to skip down.
Okay.
Did you say John, correct?
Yeah, John. Saint John.
John 10. First John?
Saint John. Oh, John. Okay, John 10.
23.
23, it says, "And Jesus walked in the
temple in Solomon's porch.
Then came the Jews round about him and
said unto him, How long doest thou make
us to doubt? If thou be the Christ, tell
us plainly."
Jesus answered them,
Uh-huh.
Go ahead. Jesus answered them, "I told
you, and ye believe not. The Father that
I the works that I do in my Father's
name, they bear witness of me.
Go ahead. But ye believe not because ye
are not of my sheep, as I said unto you.
Skip down to verse 30. Okay.
I and my Father are one.
Go ahead. Read the first verse.
to 2:35 or skip 2:35?
No, keep reading, James.
Okay. Then the Jews took up stones again
to stone him. Jesus answered them, "Many
good works have I showed you from my
Father. For which one of these works do
ye stone me?"
The Jews answered him, saying, "For a
good work we stone thee not, but for
blasphemy and because that thou, being a
man, makest thyself God." Jesus answered
them, Uh-huh. Reason And the reason they
stoned it, they said, "You a man making
yourself God." Because he said he was
the son of God. He called God his
father.
So, uh
So, that's why they said that's why we
going to stone you. But look what Jesus
replied to them with. Go ahead.
Jesus answered them, "Is it not written
in your law, I said ye are gods?
If if he called them gods unto whom the
word of God came, and the scripture
cannot be broken."
Jesus, look, it is written in your law.
We just read it. 82nd chapter of Psalms.
I said you are gods. So, if he called us
gods to whom the word of God came, and
the scripture cannot be broken.
If the scripture can't be broken, then
what are they going to become? Gods.
Blank blank. Uh That's why They call us
gods now. Let's talk about us. We are
the ones. Now, we going to
do a couple more things and then we'll
leave it alone. Let's go into Hebrews.
The first chapter and read verses six
through nine. Okay.
Hebrews 1:6-9
And again, when he bringeth into the
firstborn into the world, he saith, "And
let all the angels of God worship him."
And of the angels he saith, "Who maketh
his angels spirits and his ministers a
flame of fire."
But unto the Son he saith, "Thy throne,
O God, is forever and ever. A scepter of
righteousness is the scepter of thy
kingdom.
Thou has loved righteousness and hated
iniquity. Therefore, God, even thy God,
hath anointed thee with the oil of
gladness above all thy fellows."
So, now,
this is Jesus being called God by God.
But then, Jesus was God, but then he he
became man.
And when he died, when they crucified
him and and when he come out the grave,
he was God
again. Therefore, God called him God.
But then, Jesus
is the forerunner of us.
Let's go in the Romans.
Let's go in the Romans the 8th chapter,
read verse
28 and 29.
Okay.
Romans 8 verses 28 and 29 says, "And we
know that all things work together for
good to them that love God. To them who
are the called are the called according
to his purpose.
For whom he did
Mhm. Listen.
They are called according to his
purpose. He had a purpose for creating
us.
Yeah. So now,
we going to see
uh
what Jesus end up being. Go ahead.
For whom he did foreknow, he also did
predestinate to be conformed to the
image of his son, that he might be the
firstborn of many brethren.
Now, Jesus
It it said, "If we going to be conformed
to the image of Jesus,
because he and then and that makes him
the firstborn of many brethren. And what
did God call him? God called him God.
Yeah.
Because if you
God with strength, you are God. Let's go
to one more place.
Let's go into 1 John
3 and read verses 1 and 2.
1 John 3
and verses 1 and 2 says, "Behold, what
manner of love the Father has bestowed
upon us, that we should be called the
sons of God. Yes. Therefore, the world
knoweth us not because it knew him not.
All right. Beloved beloved, now are we
the sons of God and it doeth not yet
appear what we shall be. But we know
that when he shall appear, we shall be
like him and we shall see him as he is."
Amen. So now,
Amen. That's telling when Jesus come,
we going to be just like him.
And he is God. Therefore, we are just
then we will be God.
So what is God's purpose for creating
man? His purpose is to create God man to
become God.
That's right.
Yeah, absolutely. And and the scripture
cannot be broken.
All right.
We hope that that answered your question
as we move on to our next
Next one. Jennifer Love says, "In
Genesis 5:24,
when it says he was not for God took
him, just curious if anyone questioned
what happened to him. I know it doesn't
say, so is this one of those questions
ask God when you see him?"
Brother Julius got some light for that
question. Go ahead, brother.
No, this is not one of those questions.
This is not one of those question ask
God when you see him.
Uh the answer is in the scriptures, but
you got to do like the book say, go here
a little and there a little. So let's do
this here a little. Genesis chapter 5
James, Genesis chapter 5
and read
uh uh
verse 24.
Okay.
It says, "And Enoch walked with God
Quickly. 21.
And Enoch lived 60 and 5 years and begat
Methuselah. Uh-huh.
And Enoch walked with God after he begat
Methuselah 300 years and begat sons and
daughters. Continue. And all the days of
Enoch were 360
and 5 years. And one more. And Enoch
walked with God and he was not for God
took him. So now, he was not what?
He was not what? Now let's go there a
little. Let's go to Hebrews the 11th
chapter and let's find out what he was
not.
Okay.
Hebrews 11. And we going to start
reading at verse 5.
Okay. Hebrews 11
You don't have to wait. Here's your
answer. Go ahead.
By faith, Enoch was translated that he
should not see death. That's why God
took him. He took him and translated him
that he should not see death and was not
what? And was not found because God had
translated him.
For before his translation, he had this
testimony that he pleased God. How do
you please God? By walking with him.
Enoch walked with him for 365 years, so
God took a man in the beginning and
translated him that he should not see
death. He's still around, but he's under
invisibility, but he's still here.
That's the best we could do with that.
All right.
throw in
Let me throw in something else because
people
God took him to heaven. Go to St. John
the 3rd chapter and see what Jesus told
Nicodemus. Exactly.
The book don't say. The book say God
took him. It didn't say he took him to
heaven. St. John the 3rd chapter.
There. We going to read verses 12 and
13. Okay.
St. John 3 verse 12 and 13 says, "If I
have told you earthly things and you
believe not, how shall you believe if I
tell you of heavenly things. Mhm.
And no man hath ascended up to heaven,
but he that came down from heaven, even
the son of man which is in heaven."
There you go. So Enoch was not taken to
heaven cuz no man has ascended to heaven
except he that came down.
Right. So when he was taken, he was
taken from among man
and he
was
uh taken into the God family.
He just didn't go to heaven. He's still
walking around on this earth, but you
can't see him. Why?
Go into Let's go I think it's in the uh
Jude and show you what the Lord kept
them ages under the
chains of darkness.
That's Jude.
The book of Jude.
Right before Revelation. Oh yeah, I'm
there.
See if you can pull it up right quick. I
know it's in Jude. Jude
verse 6.
Okay.
It says, "And the angels which kept not
their first estate, but left their own
habitation, he has reserved in
everlasting chains under darkness until
the judgment of the great day."
Uh until the first resurrection when the
Lord would allow
uh bring forth the children of God.
Enoch is walking around on this earth,
but he's under chains of darkness. That
means that you can't see him.
So he took him from among men. That's
what he's talking about and brought him
into God family. For those that can see
it, Enoch
is God now.
That's all I have to say.
All right.
So we hope that shed some light for you,
Jennifer, as we move on to our next
question.
Next question. John Noel says, "I am
divor I am a divorced man
and
I am a divorced man. Am I condemned to
the pit? Can I remarry with God's
blessings?"
All right.
Guess call her.
Go to Matthew
the 5th chapter and read verse 31.
Okay.
Matthew 12
and verse 31 says,
"31 says,
Wherefore I say unto you, all manner of
sin and blasphemy shall be forgiven unto
men, but the blasphemy against the Holy
Ghost shall not be forgiven unto men."
Now, it said, "All manner of sin
can be forgiven, but the blasphemy of
the Holy Ghost
that will not be forgiven." What's the
meaning blasphemy of the Holy Ghost?
Let's go in Let's go in the Romans the
first chapter.
We're going to read from 18 to 20
and we're going to skip down to 28.
Okay. Romans 1:18 to 20 says,
"For the wrath of God is revealed from
heaven against all ungodliness and
unrighteousness of men, who hold the
truth in unrighteousness.
Because that which may be known of God
is manifest in them, for God has showed
it unto them.
For the invisible things of him from the
creation of the world are clearly seen,
being understood by the things that are
made, even his eternal power and
Godhead, so that they are without
excuse.
Now, people that is holding the truth in
unrighteousness, these are people that
has got some knowledge. Not only won't
they walk in it, they are teaching other
people not to deal with it. This is
blasphemy of the Holy Ghost. What verse
are we?
That was verse 20.
Skip down to verse 28 and read it.
And even as they did not like to retain
God in their knowledge, God gave them
over to a reprobate mind to do those
things which are not convenient.
Now, when you blaspheme the Holy Ghost,
in other words, you teach the word of
God, teach against the word of God, and
you won't live it, and you know
and understand the word of God.
So, they say even the Godhead. Not many
people understand that. So, this is the
people with great knowledge and teaches
against it. They are blaspheming against
the Holy Ghost. But with any other sin,
you can be forgiven.
Now, what you asked about can you marry
again with
God's blessing?
I say it is here.
As far
as you have As far as you have in God's
blessing,
you have to ask him that.
That's all I have to say. But if you
haven't sinned against blaspheming
against the Holy Ghost, any sin can be
forgiven.
And I'm pretty sure you can marry again,
but whether it be with God's blessing or
not,
that's between you and God.
Don't ask me to
answer for God.
Don't have to say.
All right. Hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
question.
Next question, Jennifer Love asks, "What
are the significance of the seven
spirits of God and the seven churches in
Revelation 4:5?"
Seven spirits and the seven churches.
What is the significance of that in the
Revelation 4 and 5, Brother Julius?
Let's read it.
When you get it, Revelation 4 and 5,
James. Go ahead.
And out of the throne proceedeth
lightnings and thunderings and voices.
And there were seven lamps of fire
burning before the throne, which are the
seven spirits of God. Now, these seven
spirits are angels, seven angels, okay?
And John is showing you what he saw in
the future. So, these seven spirits are
seven angels. Now, let's back up and
read
Let's go to Revelation the second
chapter.
Because you got So, you got the these
seven churches here. Let's Let's look at
these.
Uh
Revelation 2, pick it up at verse 10.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Revelation 1.
Revelation 1. Yep.
And
verse 10?
Yep.
Or okay.
I was in the spirit on the Lord's day
and heard behind me a great voice as of
a trumpet. Yeah. Saying, "I am Alpha and
Omega, the first and the last. And what
thou seest, write in a book and send it
unto the seven churches which are in
Asia, unto Ephesus, and unto Smyrna, and
unto Pergamos, and unto Thyatira, and
unto Sardis, and unto Philadelphia, and
unto Laodicea." These are the seven
churches of Asia or Asia Minor or I
would be called modern-day Turkey. And
this was
uh at that time this is where
uh what you call the new the new age
church the New Testament church and was
located be headquartered at Jerusalem,
but this are
uh seven churches that are located in
Asia. So, but the seven spirits are the
seven angels. You know, it's so it's so
much more to it, but if you read on,
each church is assigned an angel to it
in Revelation the second chapter. You
can read it on your own. But the seven
spirits are the seven angels and the
seven churches are the uh churches in
Asia Minor.
Anybody want to add to that?
All right.
Think you hit the nail on the head,
brother, as we continue to move on to
our next question.
Moving on, Most Love asks,
"In Proverbs 24:16,
it talks about a just man falling seven
times. Isn't that the same thing as
sinning willfully?"
Uh not necessarily.
I mean, sinning willfully is you know
what right is, but you go do wrong
anyway and get yourself in trouble. And
that is never a good practice. But let's
go into that Proverbs 24.
Proverbs 24. And we're going to read in
this verse that's going to talk about a
just man as well as somebody who is
unjust.
When you get there, brother, read 24
and 16.
For a just man falleth seven times and
riseth up again. But the wicked shall
fall into mischief.
Yeah, so a just man, you know, somebody
that uh
may have fell off or repented and trying
to get back on the horse and do the
thing the right way, hey, that is a good
thing. But you get some people that hey,
they wicked and they're not concerned
about repenting or trying to turn
around. But that is on them.
But you know, sometimes people can trip
you up. You can get tripped up.
You know, sometimes people sinning in
ignorance. But let's go to Ecclesiastes
9. Ecclesiastes the ninth chapter.
And let's read one verse here.
And let's see what it say, brother, in
that Ecclesiastes 9
and verse 4. Cuz if you have fallen,
like the Lord say, you get back up and
you keep running this race for eternal
life. Might as well run until time run
out. You have absolutely nothing to lose
by doing that.
Ecclesiastes 9 and what does verse 4
say?
For to him that is joined to all the
living, there is hope.
For a living dog is better than a dead
lion.
So, hey, long as there's life, there's
hope. Keep running. If you have fallen,
hey, get back up
and keep running this race and may the
Lord have mercy. That's all I got on
that.
All right. Well, hope that answered your
question there as we continue to move on
with the time check to our next one.
Yes, moving on. The time is 8:29.
Brick Brack asks,
"Are the ones that are called strangers
people who are not Israelites?
And are the nations
all Israelites that are mentioned in the
scriptures? My cousin's
church believe that Mexicans are
Israelites,
too. Could you please clarify this?"
All right. Guest caller, can you clarify
that and share some light?
Sure can. First thing is Mexicans are
not Israelites.
And the Lord called a a special uh
captivity.
In Deuteronomy the 28th chapter, we're
not going to go go through there and
read all that because it's too much to
deal with.
Deuteronomy the 28th chapter told you
what was going to happen to Israel if we
don't obey God's law.
First thing is it say we're going to
carry into all nations.
And we're going to be sold as sheep,
male and female slaves.
Then it say we're going to go into Egypt
again, which it mean the house of
bondage to us.
Mhm. By ships.
And we're going to be sold as male and
female slaves.
Now, the Mexicans did not come over here
slaves. The Mexicans have not been sold
to anybody.
But we're not going to go there. What
we're going to go is
Israel was likened unto the people.
We're going to deal with color.
First thing is
we're going to go and show you
something. We're going to show you
that Moses
the prophet
was uh
that Israel rather as a people was
likened unto the Ethiopians. So, let's
go into Amos the ninth chapter and read
verse 7.
Amos the ninth chapter
and verse 7 says, "Sorry about that.
Getting to it."
Hosea, Joel, Amos.
Is Joel
Amos? Yeah, I just passed it. Sorry
about that.
Um Amos the ninth chapter
and what verse again was that? Verse 7.
Verse 7.
Verse 7 says, "Are ye not as children of
the Ethiopians unto me, O children of
Israel?" saith the Lord.
"Have not I brought up Israel out of the
land of Egypt and the Philistines from
Caphtor and the Syrians from Kir?"
Now, the Lord asked, "Are you not as the
children of Ethiopians unto me?"
Yes, we are. Children of
the Ethiopians are black, distant
brothers.
When the Greeks looked upon the
They was They are Cushites, but when the
Greeks looked upon them, they said,
"These people have burnt faces."
From that came the word Ethiopia. From
Ethiopia came Ethiopia, black folks.
But now,
Pharaoh was trying to kill
Israel.
And Moses trying to catch up with the
baby that's supposed to be
trying to terminate rather the nation of
Israel.
And he wanted the Egyptians to kill when
the Israel had children, wanted the
Egyptians to kill all the males.
And let's go and show you that Moses
and how he was raised.
Let's go into Exodus.
The first chapter.
And first we're going to read verse 15
through 17.
And we're going to skip down and read 20
through 22. We're going to read pretty
quick cuz I have a few scriptures. Okay.
Exodus uh 1:15 through 17 says, "And the
king of Egypt spake to the Hebrew
midwives of which the name of the one
was Sephora and the name of the other
Poor. And he said, "When you do the
office of a midwife to the Hebrew women
and see them upon the stools, if it be a
son, then you shall kill him. But if it
be a daughter, then she shall live."
But the midwives uh-huh Now, he was
trying to exterminate all the Israel.
This is the Egyptian now, first chapter.
Go ahead.
But the midwives feared God and did not
as the king of Egypt commanded them, but
saved the men children alive.
Do not. When the midwife wouldn't kill
him, he put it on He told all his people
to do it. Skip down to verse 21. Read 21
and 22.
And it came to pass because the midwives
feared God that he made them houses. And
Pharaoh charged all his people saying,
"Every son that is born be cast into the
river and every daughter you shall save
alive."
Now, so Moses was done in that part.
And so he had all the Egyptians looking
over and watching the Hebrew Israelites
so they can kill every male.
So let's see what happened to Moses. How
did he escape? Let's go into Exodus the
second chapter.
Read 1 through 3 and we're going to skip
down.
Okay. Go ahead.
And there went a man of the house of
Levi and took to wife a daughter of
Levi. And the woman conceived and bare a
son. And when she saw him that he was a
godly a goodly child, she hid him 3
months. And when she could not longer
hide him, she took for him an ark of
bulrushes and dabbed it with slime and
with pitch and put the child there in.
And she laid it in the flags by the
river's brink.
Now, you weren't when she did that and
she put him in the weeds by the river's
brink. And let's see what happened. Skip
down to verse 6.
And when she had
And we And when she had opened it, she
saw the child.
Did you read verse 3?
Yes, I did.
3? Yes. Okay, so now
he was down at the river. So now
Pharaoh's daughter went down to the
river to wash herself.
And she saw that little bitty boat that
Moses' mother had made and put him in.
Now do 6. Go ahead.
And when she had opened it, she saw the
child. And behold the babe wept. And she
had compassion on him and said, "This is
one of the Hebrews' children."
Uh-huh.
Then she Then
Uh-huh. Go ahead. Keep reading.
Then said his sister to Pharaoh's
daughter, "Shall I go and call to thee a
nurse of the Hebrew women that she may
nurse the child for thee?"
Go ahead.
And Pharaoh's daughter said to her,
"Go." And the maid went and called the
child's mother.
Now, and his mother raised him, but she
was making him under the protection of
Pharaoh's daughter.
Why didn't they touch him? Skip down to
16 and go ahead.
Now, the priest of Midian had seven
daughters.
I'm I'm sorry. Keep reading.
Okay.
And Pharaoh's
him as a child. Okay? Go ahead.
And Pharaoh's said unto her, "Take the
child away and nurse it for me, and I
will give thee thy wages." And the women
And the woman took the child and nursed
it.
And And And the child grew, and she
brought him unto Pharaoh's daughter, and
he became her son. And she called his
name Moses, and she said, "Because I
drew him out of the water."
Now, let's do some reading in here.
This is Pharaoh's daughter.
She took Moses to be her son.
Now, the Egyptians are black.
That's what the word Egypt mean. When
the Greeks saw the Egyptians, saw the
Mizraimites,
they they said, "These people are
black." So they put on them the name of
of Egypt.
Now, how is it that Moses the Israelite
Hebrew Israelite can be white?
And
And And
Pharaoh is trying to kill everybody that
look like him.
And he can become Pharaoh's grandson.
That mean that Moses was the same color
as the Egyptian.
Now skip down to verse 16 and go ahead.
Now, the priest of Midian had seven
daughters. And they came and drew water
and filled the troughs to water their
father's flock.
Go ahead. And the shepherds came and
drove them away. But Moses stood up and
helped them and watered their flock.
Go ahead.
And when the And when they came to Reuel
their father, he said, "How is it that
you are come so soon today?"
And they said, "As an Egyp- an Egyptian
delivered us out of the hand of the
shepherds and also drew water enough for
us and watered the flock."
Now, the Midianites
they saw when Moses helped them and the
dad asked, "How come y'all here so
soon?"
They said, "An Egyptian helped us."
An Egyptian. So that Moses looked like
an Egyptian. That mean that Moses was
black.
Now, let's look at the Apostle Paul.
Let's go into Acts the 21st chapter.
And read verse 37 through 39.
Acts 21
verses
31 through 39.
Go ahead.
37 through 39. Okay. It says
And as Paul was to be led into the
castle, he said unto the chief captain,
"May I speak unto thee?"
Who said, "Can't Can't thou speak Greek?
Out Art not thou an Egyptian which
before these days made us an uproar and
led us out into the wilderness 4,000 men
that were murderers?"
But Paul said, "I am a man which am a
Jew of Tarsus, a city in Cilicia, a
citizen of no mean city. And I beseech
thee, suffer me to speak unto the
people."
Now, why did that Greek captain think
Paul was an Egyptian?
Because Paul was black.
Hebrew Israelites
Jews
are black.
Now, as far as the Mexicans are
concerned,
they are
white. They are the children of the
Spanish Spaniards in Spain, the European
Spanish. They come over here and they
dealt with the Aztecs and the Indians
and they had children by them, but their
daddy is a white, they are white, and
the people that call Mexicans are white,
not black. All Israelites are white.
And they look like Egyptians or
Ethiopians. So Mexicans cannot be
Israelites. They are Gentile and they
are strangers.
That's all I have to say. Yeah. And all
Israelites are
are black. He technically said white,
but he meant black.
Black.
I'm sorry.
Israelites are black. All of them.
And the Spaniards and the and the
Mexicans are white. And they are the
children of the Castilians, which is
Spanish. They have a nation in Europe
that's called Spain. That's where their
fathers come from.
Gentile and they are white.
All right.
I have to say.
Hope that answers your question as we
move on to our next question.
Uh yes, June North Ford says,
"Whenever I tell people Jesus is coming
on the earth and every eye will see him,
their response is, 'No one can see God
and live.' What should I say to that?"
Well, we know Jesus is coming to the
earth, Jerome.
Um they're actually kind of misquoting.
Um we can read out of the Bible where
Moses saw him. We can read out of the
Bible where the nation of Israel
saw him. All right. So let's go read
some verses about that. Let's go to
Exodus 34.
Cuz it don't say nobody can see God and
live. What the Bible say was no man can
see his face.
Literally see his face and live. Okay?
But let's go read it. Exodus 34.
Pick it up at 17, read to the 23.
Okay.
It says,
"Thou shalt make thee no molten gods.
The feast of unleavened bread shall thou
keep.
Seven days
thou shall eat Pardon me. You must mean
you mean 33?
33?
Yeah, and 17.
33, I'm sorry. Yeah, thank you.
33, 33 and 17? Yep. It says, "And the
Lord said unto Moses, I will do this
thing also that thou has spoken, for
thou has found grace in my sight and I
know thee by name."
And he said, "I beseech thee, show show
me thy glory."
And he said, "I will make all my
goodness pass before thee and I will
proclaim the name of the Lord before
thee and I will be gracious to whom I
will be gracious and will show mercy on
whom I will show mercy." Uh-huh.
And he said, "Thou canst not see my
face, for there shall no man see me and
live." Yeah, he's talking about his face
cuz we he going to establish that Moses
saw him. Go ahead.
And the Lord said, "Behold, there is a
place by me and thou shall stand upon a
rock. And it shall come to pass while my
glory passeth by that I will put thee in
a in a cleft of the rock and will cover
thee within my hand while I pass by. And
I will take away my hand and thou shall
see my back parts, but my face shall not
be seen." Yeah, there it is. Now, let's
go to Exodus 20 uh
24 and read verse 9 through 11.
24 verses 9 through 11 says, "Then went
up Moses and Aaron and Nadab and Abihu
and 70 of the elders. And they saw the
God of Israel. And there was under his
feet as it were a pave work of sapphire
stone and as it were the body of heaven
in its clearness." Mhm.
"And upon the nobles of the children of
Israel he laid not his hand. Also they
saw God and did eat and drink." So, they
saw God too and he didn't lay his hand
on them. They sitting there looking at
them while they eating and drinking.
Okay.
So,
yeah, they just misquoted. That's all.
That's all I got on it if anybody want
to ask.
All right. Thank you for that, brother.
As we move on to our next question, as
time is ticking, Dathan.
Yes, we are now into tonight's Q&A for
Wednesday, June the 4th, 2025.
Valencia asks,
"Is
Acts 19 verse 12 talking about those
false late night preachers asking for
money for blessed handkerchiefs?"
Mhm.
That's a old thing been going on for a
long time. Dre, what you say?
Yeah, no, it's not talking about that.
Let's start at verse 11.
Uh Acts 19 verse 11, but what you find
with them late night preachers is
they're mimicking something that was
done
to persuade people. But let's look at
that. Acts 19 verse 11. Go ahead,
brother.
"And God wrought special miracles by the
hands of Paul." So, you see it says God
wrought special miracles by the hands of
Paul. Had nothing to do with them late
night preachers. Go ahead.
"So that from his body were brought unto
the sick handkerchiefs or aprons and the
diseases departed from them and the evil
spirits went out of them."
So, you know, just like
they the the sick was healed here and
this is just something that was used.
You got folks that's mimicking this now,
them late night preachers and others,
but they are equal to what we're going
to read now. Verse 13. Go ahead.
"Then certain of the vagabond Jews
exorcists took upon them to call over
them which had evil spirits the name of
the Lord Jesus saying, 'We adjure you by
Jesus whom Paul preacheth.'" So, they
don't even know him. They talking about
the Jesus that Paul preached. Verse 15.
Go ahead.
"And the evil spirit answered and said,
'Jesus I know and Paul I know, but who
are ye?'"
Mhm. Go ahead.
"And the And the man in whom the evil
spirit was leaped on them and overcame
them and prevailed against them, so that
they fled out of that house naked and
wounded." Yeah, so them late night
preachers that's doing what they doing,
they're mimicking something that they
read here in the scriptures, but this
particular scripture is talking about
Paul and then those
coming imitating Paul and you see what
the outcome of that was. That's all I
got on that.
All right. Thank you for that. Hope that
answered their question as we move on to
our next question.
Next question. Tracy Smith says, "Women
are not supposed to teach.
Let me know what to do to make sure I
don't come off as teaching."
All right, let's go to 1 Timothy 2.
12 and 13.
1 Timothy 2. In fact,
pick it up in that verse 11.
Okay.
It says,
of the This is one of the things that
hey, keep you from coming off as
trying to act like um
teaching over congregation here. Go
ahead.
"Let the women learn in silence with all
subjection.
But I suffer not a woman to teach nor to
usurp authority over the man, but to be
in silence."
So, yeah, so you can't stand in a pulpit
and you can't be heading up no church.
Can't do that either. And also you have
to be careful on your podcasts, your
Zooms, and your other platforms that
some of the women out here holding and
doing it
on the platform the same as they would
be doing if they were inside of church.
So,
that is pretty much what the Lord said
that you're not supposed to do. You can
always edify and educate someone when it
comes to the word of God, but as far as
standing in a pulpit and being over
church and
all of that, the Lord said that is not
so. That's all I got.
Hope that answered your question. Let us
move on to our next one as time is
ticking.
Yes, next one. Normal Norman Nix asks,
"What is meant by ye shall have
tribulations 10 days in Revelations 2
verse 10?"
Let's go to Revelations 2 and 10. And
we'll go ask the guest caller, "What is
that meant when they say you shall have
tribulation for 10 days?"
Okay. Well, Revelation uh
Revelation 2 verse 10 says, "Fear none
of those things which thou shall suffer.
Behold, the devil shall cast some of you
into prison that ye may be tried and ye
shall have tribulation 10 days. Be thou
faithful unto death and I will give thee
a crown of life."
Well, I know about 3 and 1/2 years of
great tribulation
that the Lord is going to allow Satan to
bring upon this
earth through the beast and the false
prophet.
But as far as tribulation 10 days, I
don't have a clue.
Can't answer it.
I have no way to define
Okay. We'll leave it right there as we
move on to our next question.
Next question. Sandra Allen says, "Could
you please explain what the flaming
swords are in Genesis 3 verse 24?"
Why don't we go to Genesis 3 and 24?
And when you get there, brother, then
the guest caller will share some light
on the term flaming swords.
Okay.
Genesis 3 and 24 says, "So he drove out
the man and he placed at the east of the
garden of Eden cherubims and a flaming
sword which turned every way to keep the
way of the tree of life."
Well, it says what it says.
It says flaming swords.
So, anything under the anything beyond
that
is speculation.
Why can't it be what it said?
It's flaming swords.
Don't have to say. Yeah.
A sword in flame combined. All right.
We'll leave it right there and keep
moving on to our next question and these
questions here, let's open them up to
the panel because time is ticking for
us. Go right ahead, sister Dathan.
All right. Sister Tanisha says, "I
understand that nowhere in the Bible
does it say smoking cigarettes is a sin.
I read that some of the cigarette brands
use pig's blood to make the filters. My
question is would smoking cigarettes
make us unclean by smoking them?
Leviticus 11:7
and 8 are given."
All right. Let's go Leviticus 11
through 8.
And I noticed you said that um
that you read that
and sometimes you have to always
double-check your source. But, let's go
to Revelation, I mean, I'm sorry,
Leviticus 11. Read that 7 and 8,
brother, and then let's open it up to
the panels.
It says,
"And the swine, though he divide the
hoof and be cloven-footed, yet he
cheweth not the cud, he is unclean to
you.
Of their flesh shall ye not eat, and
their carcass shall ye not touch. They
are unclean to you."
Julius, you're on mute.
Yeah, just said what it mean. You can't
eat their flesh. Can't touch their dead
bodies.
Yeah, and if the cigarettes is made from
uh filters
is made from pig's blood and you want to
smoke cigarettes, maybe you should roll
them up
without the filter.
We don't condone smoking, but smoking is
not sin. Sin is a transgression of the
law.
That's it.
Yeah, that's correct. So,
that's all we got on that as we move on
to our next question.
Next question, Randy seems asked for you
to explain Mark 16:16-18.
Are any of these things going on today?
Let's go see that Mark 16:16.
And yes, I didn't see where the Lord put
a time limit on that, but let's read it.
Mark 16
and 16.
Okay. He says, "He that believeth and is
baptized shall be saved, but he that
believeth not shall be damned. Uh-huh.
And these signs shall follow them that
believe. In my name shall they cast out
devils. They shall speak with new
tongues. They shall take up serpents,
and if they drink any deadly thing, it
shall not hurt them.
They shall lay hands on the sick, and
they shall recover."
Yep. So,
know the people who are supposed to get
baptized, and yeah, they're still doing
that today.
But, as far as being saved, they got to
cross the finish line, but open to the
panel.
Well,
what do you got? We just dealt with some
of that.
I will
for as they're going to be uh when it's
talking about uh uh
speaking with uh new tongues, it didn't
say other tongues.
New tongues. Let's take this down today.
Let's go into Colossians the third
chapter.
We're going to read from 8 to 10.
Colossians
Three?
Three and verses 8 to 10 says,
"But now, ye also put off all these,
anger, wrath, malice, blasphemy, filthy
communication out of your mouth.
Lie not one to another, seeing that ye
have put off the old man with his deeds,
and have put on the new man, which is
renewed in knowledge after the image of
him that created him."
What verses there? That was verses 8
through 10.
Okay, well, you got to put on new man,
you know, and and uh you clean your
conversation up.
See, that is a
uh that's when you're talking about uh
having a
uh uh New tongues.
No,
you know, speaking a new language. You
uh
you know, another tongue.
I mean say not another tongue. What does
it say?
A uh
new tongue.
Mhm.
you don't do all this. Don't talk when
you're serving the God like you talk
when you was off in the streets.
Now, let's go into Psalms the 50th
chapter and read verse 23.
Okay.
Psalm 50 and verse 23
says,
"Whosoever
offereth praise glorifyeth
me. And to him that ordereth his
conversation aright will I show the
salvation of God."
So, because you're speaking in a in a
new tongue now, you ain't condemning
lying and and bearing false witness on
people and cursing people out and all
that kind of stuff. You're speaking with
a new tongue. In other words, you you
changed your conversation.
Ephesians the fourth chapter and verses
19 through 25.
Okay. Ephesians the fourth chapter
fourth chapter verses 19 through 25
says,
"Who being past feeling have given
themselves over unto lasciviousness to
work all uncleanliness
with greediness. But, ye have not so
learned Christ.
If so be that ye have heard him and have
been taught by him as the truth is in
Jesus.
That ye put off concerning the former
conversation, the old man, which is
corrupt according to the deceitful lust.
And be renewed in the spirit of your
mind.
Now,
And that ye In other words, Mhm. Go
ahead.
And that ye put That This is verse 24.
Go ahead.
"And that ye put on the new man, which
after God is created in righteousness
and true holiness.
25?
"Wherefore, putting away lying, speak
every man truth with his neighbor, for
we are members one of another."
So, now, that mean if you uh
speaking
with a new tongue, not another tongue.
Your conversation is cleaned up. It's
all that simple.
Now, as far as the sick is concerned,
do it.
I know of some people that have been
prayed over
and anointed,
and they was healed.
Yes, sir.
And and and uh and nowadays, we are
still casting out spirits, but not like
with the like not with the drama it was
in the days of Jesus and Paul there.
Because something So, you just have to
understand that there more than one way
to cast out devils.
So, let's go into Matthew the eighth
chapter, and we're going to read verse
16.
Matthew 8 and verse 16 says,
"When the evening was come, they brought
unto him many that were possessed with
devils. And he cast out the spirits with
his word, and healed all that were
sick."
So, now, the physical part of it, the
dramatic part of it, when they brought
Jesus,
he cast out devils, but it's one thing
people overlook.
He cast out these spirits
with his word.
And we do it every time we go and preach
to somebody
and they turn away from evil doing and
start walking in God's law, you have
cast that evil spirit out of them. Yes,
sir.
And you made them a new person.
The The dramatics is not there.
But, that's why you go to church
every Sabbath day
because you listen, and after a while, a
change setting on you.
And the evil and wicked thing that you
used to doing, you don't do that no
more. You stop.
Yes,
But, that's still going on. Devils are
being cast out by the word of God.
But, as far as being
uh
uh uh
bit by poisonous snakes
and drinking poison and not dying from
it, I have not seen that, so I don't
have no no comment on it.
Yeah, all right. We're going to leave it
right there. Sister Deborah, go try and
get us another question or two in
quickly. Go right ahead.
All right, Deborah Parsha says,
"After reading 1 Corinthians 11:14,
I got on my adult son about cutting off
his hair, his long hair. He said this
scripture doesn't pertain to men today.
Please share some light that I may know
the truth. 1 Corinthians 11:14."
We'll read it, James, when you get
there, and let's open it up to the
panel.
It says, "Doeth not even nature itself
teach you that if a man have long hair,
it is a shame unto him?
Now, that didn't say it that that didn't
say that the law said. You understand?
Yeah. Paul is making an example of
nature, but he didn't say
it is commanded because Absalom, one of
David's sons, had long hair.
Yeah. Then again, you look at Samson.
His strength was in his long hair.
Right.
And we don't have nothing to say a man
can't have long hair. What it is that
Paul is using as an example say nature
show you it is a shame.
A shame to who?
Right.
against the law.
Therefore, it's not sin.
That's all I have to say. All right. And
our final question of the evening,
Sister Deborah, what is it?
Yes, Tracy Smith says, I have a
question. I can't remember the book and
verse, but example, you give someone
money, should you expect it back? Not
even God would loan it to him.
What's that question again? Yeah, one
more time for that. Right. She says, I
can't remember the book or the verse,
but for example, you give someone money,
should you expect it back? Then she
says, not even God would loan it to him.
You're You're saying you give somebody
money.
Do you put
loan in it?
Are you A A loan is something that
that's supposed to be paid back.
If you give and you have a conversation,
y'all come to an agreement, that's two
different things.
That's it. If you give it If you give it
to him, you should not expect it back.
But if you loan it to him, then you
expect it back cuz it's in Psalms where
it says, I can't call it right now. He
said, "The wicked borrow and pay not
back again." Um 37. Psalm 37 verse 21.
Okay, 37.
Psalm 37 verse 21 says,
"The wicked borroweth and prayeth not
and payeth not again, but the righteous
showeth mercy and giveth."
Okay. Do not If it's a loan,
and they ain't paying it back, then the
Lord call them wicked. But then if you
give it to him, then you're righteous
and you're showing mercy.
Yes, sir.
That's all I have to say.
Yeah. Sometimes you have to be careful
and only loan what you can afford
and expect not to get back in some
cases.
All right.
We hope that that answered your
question.
And Sister Deborah, time check.
Yes, the time is 9:05.
We have ran out of time. We want to
thank everybody from all around the
world who joined in with us this
evening.
It was fun to take part in answering
your questions. And we say if you
submitted a question and we didn't have
a chance to get to it, please don't
resubmit it. Sister Deborah take your
question, put it in rotation, and we
will deal with that next Wednesday. So,
until we all come together again, be
blessed, be safe, and may the Lord have
mercy on us all and stay prayed up as
Brother James closes us out.
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name. Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread, and
forgive us our debts as we forgive our
debtors. And lead us not into
temptation, but deliver us from evil.
For thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever. In Jesus' name we
pray. Amen.